page1solutions.com 2010-05-22

# Page 1 Solutions, LLC - Privacy Policy

his privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for (www.Page1Solutions.com). It applies solely to information collected by this website and will notify you of the following:

  1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared
  2. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data
  3. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information
  4. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information

**Information Collection, Use, and Sharing**

We collect only information that you voluntarily give us via email or in other direct contact. Specifically, that would be:

  * Your first and last name
  * Your email address
  * Your telephone number(s)

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We have access to/collect only information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

We will use your information to respond to you and evaluate the possibility of working with you on a website project. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order or to facilitate the use of our Blog which is hosted by a third party. 

But we reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials and new products or services. 

**Your Access to and Control Over Information**  
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the contact form or phone number given on our website:

  * See what data we have about you, if any.
  * Change/correct any data we have about you.
  * Have us delete any data we have about you.
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

**If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 800-916-3886 or via[email](http://www.page1solutions.com/contact.html).**

**Security**  
We take precautions to protect your information. We use all the latest security techniques and do not collect sensitive information (such as credit card data) via the website.

In addition, we protect our clients' websites utilizing managed hosting with Rackspace, also behind a Cisco ASA firewall with 512-bit encryption, and we use SSL protocols to protect all information gathered on their websites.

We collect and store information through log files to help stop spammers from sending us junk email. We do not tie your personally identifiable information to information in the log files. This is simply an additional means of preventing robots or spammers from sending us form submissions.

**Legal Disclosure**  
We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website.

**Links**  
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.

We use both first party and third party cookies and both session ID and persistent cookies. The first party cookies were created by Page 1 Solutions and are used to make it easier for you to navigate our site. The third party cookies are used by other companies, such as Google, to track website traffic information or location information for more accurate map directions.

A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file.

**Changes in this Privacy Policy**  
We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time including what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you by means of a notice on this page.

**Testiminials**  
We post customer testimonials on our website which may contain personally identifiable information such as the customer's name. Before posting any testimonial, we do obtain the customer's consent to post their name along with their testimonial.

**Page 1 Solutions is a TRUSTe Licensed Site**  
Page 1 Solutions is a licensee of the TRUSTe Web Privacy Seal Program. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build users’ trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the website www.Page1Solutions.com. Because this website wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Bill Fukui at [info@page1solutions.com](mailto:info@page1solutions.com). If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or if your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contact TRUSTe at <http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php> TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns.

### Page 1 Solutions

17301 W. Colfax Ave, Suite #275,   
Golden, CO 80401  
**Effective Date:** 08/01/2008
